<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | ThreeWheeler</title>
    <link>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://threewheeler.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We work on machine learning and deep learning methods for intelligent transportation systems. We are generally interested in transportation mode detection and traffic flow prediction based on spatio-temporal data and methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any ideas about this field and its related machine learning or deep learning methods, please mail us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/fyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/fyc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;blablabla&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/qyj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/qyj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yanjun Qin is currently pursuing the Ph.D. degree with the School of Software Engineering, Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications, China. Her current main interests include location based services, pervasive computing, convolution neural networks and machine learning. And mainly engaged in traffic pattern recognition related project research and implementation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/wcx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://threewheeler.github.io/authors/wcx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a post graduate student in Beijing University of Posts and Telecomunications, working in the Institute of Computing Technology of the Chinese Academy of Sciences. I work on machine learning and deep learning methods for intelligent transportation systems. I&amp;rsquo;m generally interested in transportation mode detection and traffic flow prediction based on spatio-temporal data and methods. If you have any ideas about this field and its related machine learning or deep learning methods, please mail me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, I&amp;rsquo;m currently the CTO of Finerit.com. It is welcomed to discuss any technical issues with me using email.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
